Sewall Wright Papers 1895-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.60
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1895-1988; 13.5 Linear feet
  - Jonsson, Per, 1969 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jordan, W.K., 1944 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jordon, C., 1957 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1931-56 (Box Series I-13)
    Hutchins, Marjorie; Smith, Austin
  - Journal of the American Statistical Association, 1962 (Box Series I-13)
    Cornfield, Jerome; Gillispie, Charles
  - The Journal of Genetics-Cook, Robert C., 1940 (Box Series I-13)
    Cook, Robert C.
  - Journal of Experimental Zoology (Box Series I-13)
    - Butler, E.G., 1953-54 (Box Series I-13)
    - Harrison, Ross G., 1931-53 (Box Series I-13)
    - Hisaw, F.L., 1954 (Box Series I-13)
    - Kaufman, B.P., 1946 (Box Series I-13)
    - Koprowski, Hilary, 1963 (Box Series I-13)
    - Nicholas, John, 1947-62 (Box Series I-13)
    - Willens, Sally, 1963 (Box Series I-13)
    - Schewe, Edgar R., 1963 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journal of Heredity of the American Genetic Association (Box Series I-13)
    - Cook, Robert C., 1926-54 (Box Series I-13)
      Morgan, T.H.
    - Dunn, L.C., 1933 (Box Series I-13)
    - Lake, Barbara, 1953-55 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journal of Morphology, 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Adelman, Howard B., 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Butler, E.G., 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Coker, R. E., 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Hamburger, Viktor, 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Hisaw, F.L., 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    - Pollister, Arthur W., 1947 (Box Series I-13)
  - Journa1 of Theoretical Biology (Box Series I-13)
    - Cadenhead, M., 1962 (Box Series I-13)
    - Danielli, F. R. S., 1960-63 (Box Series I-13)
    - Wolpert, Lewis, 1962-63 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jull, Morley A., 1945 (Box Series I-14)
  - Junk, W., 1937 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kacser, H., 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaiser, Harold, 1931-32 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kalckar, Herman M., 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Källén, Bengt, 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kalmus, H., 1951 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kammerer, Ruth, 1957-58 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kämpe, Y., 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaplan, Karen Michelle, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Karlin, Samuel, 1963-1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kaufmann, Berwind P., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Keeler, Clyde, 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kehs, Kent DI, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    Little Brown and Co.
  - Kellerman, Karl F., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kellogg, Charles E., 1917 (Box Series I-14)
    Aldrich, A. W.
  - Kellogg, Vernon, 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kemp, W.B., 1924-42 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kempthorne, Oscar, 1952-75 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kendall/Hunt Publishing Co., 1970 (Box Series I-14)
    Timlin, Gerie
  - Kendrick, John F., 1944 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kennan, George, 1920 (Box Series I-14)
    Fairchild
  - Kerr, Warwick Estevam, 1966-69 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kerster, Harold William, 1958-59 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kessel, Raymond, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Key, Wilhelmine Enteman, 1924-54 (Box Series I-14)
  - Khorana, H. Gobind, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Khrlich, Richard, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Khurana, Jagmohan Singh, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kiddy, Charles A., 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kidwell, James F., 1963-66 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kikkawa, H., 1959 (Box Series I-14)
    Kimura, Motoo
  - Killough, D.T., 1926 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kimball, A. W., 1956-57 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A., 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kimura, Motoo, 1966 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Jack Lester, 1965-78 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Robert G., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - King, Willford I., 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kinsey, Alfred C., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kirby, Greg C., 1973-75 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kislovsky, D., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kitzmiller, James B., 1965 (Box Series I-14)
  - Klauber, L. M., 1937 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kleinholz, Lewis H., 1956 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kline, George L., 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kloepfer, H. Warner, 1940 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knight, Frank H., 1934-35 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knisely, Melvin H., 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knobel, Gratia Esher, 1937 (Box Series I-14)
  - Knowles, P.F., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Koch, Helen, 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Koehm, Richard, 1979-80 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kojima, Ken-Ichi, 1964-70 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kolin, Alexander, 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kollros, Jerry J., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Koprowski, Hilary, 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kornhauser, S. II, 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kotsovsky, D., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krasnoff, R., 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krause, J.T., 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Krichesky, Boris, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kroker, Hans, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kubitschek, H.E., 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kunkel, B.W., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Kupzov, A.J., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - LaForge, Karl, 1979 (Box Series I-14)
  - LaForge, Steven, 1976-77 (Box Series I-14)
  - LaHam, Quentin N., 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Laird, Anna Kane, 1965 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lamotte, Maxime, 1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lancaster Press Inc., 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - Landahl, H.D., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Landauer, Walter, 1925-[5]2 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lande, Russ, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Landsteiner, Karl, 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Langer, R.E., 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lanham, Urless N., 1947-54 (Box Series I-14)
  - LaRue, George R., 1947-48 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lasker, Gabriel, 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lasley, John F., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Laughlin, H[arry] H[amilton], 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Laughnan, John R., 1944-65 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lauprecht, Edwin, 1958-64 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lawson, C. A., 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Layrisse, Miguel, 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lazerett, B.G., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Leash, Aaron M., n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Leavens, Dickson H., 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1954-1973; 3.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Avery, Oswald Theodore; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Leon J. Cole Professor of Genetics; Molecular genetics; Publication; Watson, James D.
  - Lemon, Jas. E. and Son, 1919 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lerner, I. Michael (Isadore Michael), 1932-1952; 10.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Fellowships, assistantships; Genetics -- Birds; Physiology; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - LeRoy, Henri Louis, 1961-69 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levene, Howard, 1947-69 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levin, Simon A., 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levinton, Jeffrey, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levit, S.G., 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levitan, Max, 1954-70 (Box Series I-14)
  - Levitt, Paul, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewandowski, Josef, 1923 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewis, David J., 1935-37 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewis, E.B., n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewis, Richard S., 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lewontin, Richard C., 1959-1977; 9.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    American Association for the Advancement of Science; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; History of biology, especially genetics; Population genetics; Publication; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Wallace, Bruce
  - Li, Ching Chun, 1944-1977; 28.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Liljedahl, Lars-Erik
    American Institute of Biological Sciences; Behavioral genetics, IQ; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Li, Clara L., 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Li, Jerome C.R., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - Li, Wen-Hsiung, 1975-79 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lieth, H., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lillie, Frank R., 1925-45 (Box Series I-14)
  - Liljedahl, Lars-Erik, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lindsley, D.L., 1963 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lindstrom, E[rnest] W., 1923-36 (Box Series I-14)
  - [Linnberg, H.], 1949 (Box Series I-14)
    Nachtsheim, Hans
  - Lipman, Charles B., 1943 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lipscomb, S. R., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - Little, C[larence] C[ook], 1918-1956; 28.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Little, "Pete"; Cattell, J. McKeen
    Cancer, chemotherapy; Cattell, James McKeen; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics -- Nomenclature; Medical research; Recommendations; Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory
  - Little Brown and Co., 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Livengood, W., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lloyd, Monte, 1956 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lloyd, Stuart, 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Loeb, Leon, 1921 (Box Series I-14)
  - Loftis, J.R., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
    Office of the Secretary of Defense
  - Logan, A.C., 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Long, Esmond R., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Long Island Biological Association (Box Series I-14)
    - Long Island Biological Association, 1934 (Box Series I-14)
    - Demerec, M., 1951 (Box Series I-14)
    - Flem, Dorothy V., 1951 (Box Series I-14)
    - Warren, Katherine Brehme, 1955-56 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lonnquist, John H., 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Loomis, D.W., 1933 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lorenz, Egon, 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lorimer, Frank, 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lotka, Alfred J., 1930-46 (Box Series I-14)
  - Louisiana State University, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
    Smith, Charles E.
  - Lowdermilk, W.C., 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lowrie, Donald, 1956-58 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lu, Fuo-Hwa, 1954-56 (Box Series I-14)
  - Luce, Wilbur M., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Luckhardt, Arno B., 1939 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ludmerer, Kenneth M., 1970-71 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ludwig, Archie, 1963 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ludwin, I., 1948 -49 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lukert, Ronald A., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Luria, Salvador E., 1947-1959; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Gordon, Robert Dean
  - Lurie, Max B., 1932-33 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lush, Jay, 1918-65 (Box Series I-14)
  - Luticoff, 1933 (Box Series I-14)
  - Luttrell, J. Hart, 1941 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lyman, Sally, 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lynch, Clara J., 1966 (Box Series I-14)
  - Lyon, Channing B., 1939-43 (Box Series I-14)
  - Maas, Werner, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mabe, Paul, 1932 (Box Series I-14)
  - MacArthur, John W., 1932-42 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mack, J.E., 1959 (Box Series I-14)
  - Maclise, Marion, 1943 (Box Series I-14)
  - McAtee, W.L., 1928-32 (Box Series I-14)
  - McClung, C[larence] E., 1933 (Box Series I-14)
  - McConnell, F. A., 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - McDonald, D.J., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - McDougall, Mary Stuart, 1945 (Box Series I-14)
  - McElroy, W.D., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - McEwen, Gee. F., 1921 (Box Series I-14)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1964-66 (Box Series I-14)
    Boggs, William E.; Greene, Jay E.
  - McKusick, Victor A., 1962-64 (Box Series I-14)
  - McMahan, Wayne J., 1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - The Macmillan Company, 1934 (Box Series I-14)
    McCurdy, H. B.; Morehouse, T.C.
  - McMurray, O.L., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - McNeill, [John T.?], n.d. (Box Series I-14)
  - McPhee, Hugh C., 1931-54 (Box Series I-14)
  - McPherson, Donald A., 1946-47 (Box Series I-14)
  - Magalhaes, Luiz Edmundo, 1965 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mainland, Gordon B., 1946-53 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mainx, Felix, 1935-47 (Box Series I-14)
  - Major, Jack, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Malecot, G., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Malisoff, W.M., 1933 (Box Series I-14)
    Philosophy of Science
  - Mangelsdorf, A. J., 1932-49 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mangelsdorf, Paul, 1944-47 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mankins, Jerry, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Manning, E.W., 1943 (Box Series I-14)
    Mrs. T.H. Manning
  - Margolis, Otto S., 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Marine, Gene, 1958 (Box Series I-14)
  - Marschak, Jacob, 1946 (Box Series I-14)
    Cowles Commission for Research in Economics
  - Marshak, Alfred, 1945 (Box Series I-14)
  - Marston, H.W., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
    McPhee, Hugh C.
  - Maruyama, Takeo, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
  - Masson, E., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mathematical Reviews, 1966 (Box Series I-14)
    Berberian, S.K.
  - Mather, Kenneth, 1963 (Box Series I-14)
  - Matson, G. Albin, 1941 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mattingly, John W., 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mauer, Irving, 1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - Maxson, Stephen G., 1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Maxwell, Kenneth E., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - May, Stephen, 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mayer, Joseph, 1954-55 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mayr, Ernst, 1944-1951; 7.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Population genetics; Publication -- Society for the Study of Evolution
  - Medawar, P.B., 1947-48 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mehlberg, Henry, 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - Meisler, Samuel H., 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mendosa, Mayo, 1921 (Box Series I-14)
  - Merillat, L.A., 1924 (Box Series I-14)
  - Merrick, James L., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mettelman, Waiter H., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Metz, Charles W., 1929-54 (Box Series I-14)
  - Michigan State College, 1955 (Box Series I-14)
    Hannah, John H.; Honorary Doctor of Science Degree
  - Michod, Richard, 1975-80 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miles, Stephen B., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miller, Alden H., 1943-55 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miller, Arnold R., 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miller, Brewster S., 1948-49 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Miller, James R., 1964 (Box Series I-14)
  - Millin, R.B., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - Minnich, D.E., 1932-47 (Box Series I-14)
  - Minsk, Gertrude G., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - Misroch, S. Leslie, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mitchell, Alan L., 1936 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mitchell, William S., 1935 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moe, Henry Alien, 1935-57 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moebes, K. G. Warner, 1954 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mohat, H.R., 1931 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mohler, J.R., 1925-34 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mohr, Otto L., 1945 (Box Series I-14)
  - Montalenti, G., 1948-70 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moore, Carl R., 1935-55 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moore, D., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
    Grahame Book Co. Pty. Ltd.
  - Moore, George T., 1944 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moore, John A., 1951-80 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moore, Ruth, 1953 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moran, Joseph Francis, 1919 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moree, Ray, 1951-53 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morgan, Ann H., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morgan, Thomas H., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morgan, Waiter C., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar, 1965 (Box Series I-14)
    Beadle, George
  - Morley, Fred H. W., 1949-53 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morrison, Donald F., 1965 (Box Series I-14)
  - Morton, Newton, 1972-80 (Box Series I-14)
  - Moshinsky, Pearl, 1940 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mott, N.F., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mullen, Frances A., 1939 (Box Series I-14)
  - Muller, Herman J., 1928-1967; 29.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Biographical and personal data; Biographical and personal data -- Obituary; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Muller, Hermann Joseph. 70th birthday; Drosophila genetics; Educational matters; Fellowships, assistantships; Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Genetics -- Animals; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Human genetics; International Congress of Genetics -- Seventh Congress; Levit, Solomon G.; National Academy of Sciences -- Committee activities; Population genetics; Radiation genetics; Requests for reprints; Russian politics and science; Serebrovsky, Alexander Sergeevich; Society for the Study of Evolution; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; University of Chicago
  - Muller, Mrs, Herman J. (Thea), 1967-1974 (Box Series I-14)
  - Mundkur, Balajii D., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Munger, Elizabeth, 1959 (Box Series I-14)
    Perspectives in Biology and Medicine
  - Munro, S.S., 1934-64 (Box Series I-14)
  - Murchie, Guy, 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Murie, Adolph, 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Murlin, John R., 1932 (Box Series I-14)
  - Murphy, M. Janice, 1947 (Box Series I-14)
  - Musser, Karl B., 1922 (Box Series I-14)
  - Myslivec, Vaclav, 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Naglaki, Tnomas, 1974-78 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nasarenko, 1930 (Box Series I-14)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1945-1979; 36 folders (Box Series I-14)
    Babcock, Ernest Brown; Business; Castle, William Ernest; Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; East, Edward Murray; Glass, Bentley; Lewontin, Richard Charles; National Academy of Sciences; Publication; Wilson, Edwin Bidwell
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1950-68 (Box Series I-14)
    - Babcock, E.R., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
    - Bronk, Detlev W., 1959 (Box Series I-14)
    - Brown, Harrison, 1963 (Box Series I-14)
    - Castle, William E., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
    - Citizens League Against Sonic Boom, 1968 (Box Series I-14)
    - Compton, Arthur H., 1936 (Box Series I-14)
    - East, E[dward] M[urray], 1935 (Box Series I-14)
    - Edsall, John T., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
    - Eisner, T., 1971 (Box Series I-14)
    - Emerson, Alfred E., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Gilbertson, Edna, 1961 (Box Series I-14)
    - Glass, Bentley, 1965 (Box Series I-14)
    - Gregory, Wilham K., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
    - Hamburger, Viktor, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Hausler, Dorothea, 1962 (Box Series I-14)
    - Hudson, N. Paul, 1936 (Box Series I-14)
    - Irwin, M. Robert, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Lewontin, Richard C., 1968 (Box Series I-14)
    - Lindsley, Dan L., 1979 (Box Series I-14)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C., 1945 (Box Series I-14)
    - Meld, G.D., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
    - Northrup, John H., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Romer, Alfred S., 1950-51 (Box Series I-14)
    - Rossi, Bruno, n. d. (Box Series I-14)
    - Shockley, W., 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Spector, William S., 1955-56 (Box Series I-14)
    - Sporn, Philip, 1969 (Box Series I-14)
    - Tax, Sol, 1959 (Box Series I-14)
    - Tuve, Merle, 1968-69 (Box Series I-14)
    - Wald, George, n. d. (Box Series I-14)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1971 (Box Series I-14)
    - Wetmore, [F.] A[lexander], 1945 (Box Series I-14)
    - Williams, Josephine A., 1962-68 (Box Series I-14)
    - Wilson, Edwin B., 1937-50 (Box Series I-14)
    - Wright, Fred E., 1934-47 (Box Series I-14)
  - National Council of American- Society Friendship Inc., 1943 (Box Series I-14)
    Smith, Edwin S.
  - National Publishing Co., 1959 (Box Series I-14)
  - National Research Council, 1931-1973; 21 folders (Box Series I-14)
    Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Demerec, Milislav; Fellowships, assistantships; National Research Council; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
    - Barnum, Susie C., 1931-36 (Box Series I-14)
    - Cannan, R, Keith, 1955 (Box Series I-14)
    - Chapman, H.B., 1936 (Box Series I-14)
    - Curtis, W[interton] C[onway], 1931 (Box Series I-14)
    - Demerec, Milislav, 1945 (Box Series I-14)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
    - Elliot, Edith, 1921 (Box Series I-14)
    - Herman, Inger, 1963 (Box Series I-14)
    - Hill, Berton, 1956-57 (Box Series I-14)
    - Irwin, M, Robert, 1963 (Box Series I-14)
    - Johnson, Duncan S., 1931-32 (Box Series I-14)
    - Lapp, C.J., 1952 (Box Series I-14)
    - Lewis, Ivey F., 1933-35 (Box Series I-14)
    - Lillie, Frank S., 1931 (Box Series I-14)
    - McAdams, Robert, 1973 (Box Series I-14)
    - Morris, J.C., 1942 (Box Series I-14)
    - Payne, Fernandus, 1932-33 (Box Series I-14)
    - Robbins, William J., 1933 (Box Series I-14)
    - Rubey, William W., 1952 (Box Series I-14)
    - VanEvera, B.D., 1947 (Box Series I-14)
    - Winters, L[awrence] M[erriam], 1933-34 (Box Series I-14)
  - National Science Foundation, 1952-1981; 13 folders (Box Series I-14)
    Committee activities; Gillespie, John H.; National Science Foundation; Population genetics; Research support; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Advisory Committee, Biological and Medical Sciences (Box Series I-14)
    - Bethel, James S., n.d. (Box Series I-14)
    - Consolazio, Wilham K., 1952 (Box Series I-14)
    - Gillespie, John H., 1981 (Box Series I-14)
    - Green, Margaret C., 1954 (Box Series I-14)
    - Kaufman, Donald W., 1978 (Box Series I-14)
    - Kelly, Harry C., 1959 (Box Series I-14)
    - Keogstad, Blanchard O., 1958 (Box Series I-14)
    - Leferve, George Jr., 1957-1958 (Box Series I-14)
    - Parker, Dean A., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
    - Potter, J, G., 1960 (Box Series I-14)
    - Sprugel, George Jr., 1958-63 (Box Series I-14)
    - Waterman, Alan, 1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nature, 1950-51 (Box Series I-14)
  - Naylor, Alfred F., 1957-67 (Box Series I-14)
  - Neel, James V., 1939-1965; 5.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-14)
    Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Human genetics; Population genetics; Stalker, Harrison Dailey
  - Nei, Masatoshi, 1967-81 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nelson, C. W., 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - The Nevada Engineer, 1970 (Box Series I-14)
    Gofman, John W.; Tamplin, Arthur R.
  - Nevo, Eviatar, 1977 (Box Series I-14)
  - The New York Academy of Sciences, 1946-66 (Box Series I-14)
    Gordon, Myron; Miner, Eunice Thomas
  - New York Life Insurance Co., 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1949-51 (Box Series I-14)
    Gordon, Myron
  - Newman, H[oratio] H[ackett], 1921 (Box Series I-14)
  - Neyman, J[erzy], 1944-71. (Box Series I-14)
  - Nicholas, John S., 1946-63 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nicholson Hill Bookstore, 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ninth International Congress of Genetics, 1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nityagopal, H., 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Niver, George E., 1942 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nordby, Julius E., 1943 (Box Series I-14)
  - Norman, A[rthur] G[eoffrey], 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - North Carolina State College, 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Norton, H.W, Jr., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Norton, Horace W., 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Novitski, Edward, 1939-41 (Box Series I-14)
  - Nyberg, Dennis, 1976 (Box Series I-14)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1948 (Box Series I-14)
    Holleander, Alexander
  - Obaidi, M., 1978 (Box Series I-14)
  - O'Brien, John P., 1949 (Box Series I-14)
  - Ochando, M.D., 1973 (Box Series I-14)
  - Odell, Ted, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Odonald, Peter, 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Offermann, Carlos A., 1934 (Box Series I-14)
  - Oldfield, Margery, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - Oliver, Clarence P., 1954-57 (Box Series I-14)
    American Society for Human Genetics
  - Olmsted, Charles E., 1950-51 (Box Series I-14)
  - Olson, Everett C., 1952 (Box Series I-14)
    Paleozoology Committee
  - Opichal, Mojmir, 1946 (Box Series I-14)
  - Orlov, Michael, 1976-77 (Box Series I-14)
  - Orzack, Steven, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
  - OSC Cooperative Association, 1957 (Box Series I-14)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, 1931-34 (Box Series I-14)
  - Osborne, Richard H., 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Osterhout, W., 1949-50 (Box Series I-14)
  - Oxford University-Weldon Memorial Prize, 1947-48 (Box Series I-14)
    Melville, P. C.; Hendry, A.
  - Pagano, Jorge E., 1955 (Box Series I-14)
  - Painter, T[heophilus] S., 31937 (Box Series I-14)
  - Paleobiology, 1980 (Box Series I-14)
    Schoff, Thomas J. M.; Hopson, James A.
  - Panisset, Maurice, 1960 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pao, W.K., 1948 (Box Series I-14)
  - Park, Orlando, 1952 (Box Series I-14)
  - Park, Thomas, 1934-72 (Box Series I-14)
  - Parzen, Emanuel, 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pasquale, Lynne, 1961 (Box Series I-14)
  - Patterson, J[ohn] T[homas], 1947-52 (Box Series I-14)
  - Patterson, Neil, 1965 (Box Series I-14)
  - Paul, Katharine H., 1932 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1962 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pavan, C., 1946-54 (Box Series I-14)
  - Peacock, A.D., 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pearson, Egon S., 1931-76 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pearson, F[rank] A[shmore], 1923-25 (Box Series I-14)
  - Pease, Roger W, Jr., 1967 (Box Series I-14)
  - Peau, Michael, 1950 (Box Series I-14)
  - Peckham, Morse, 1954 (Box Series I-14)